http://www.football-bookmakers.com/privacy.php

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is composed of the several sections. Each of the sections is equally important, so we encourage you to carefully read all of them before you consent to the processing of your personal data.
What information can be found in this Policy?
Introduction
Data Controller and Data Subjects
Data we process
Why we process your data and how
Our use of cookies
How we protect your data
Legal ground for processing your data
Who else may access your data
Transfer of your data to third countries
Your rights?
Introduction
When you visit this website we might be processing some of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is important to you to understand how your personal data is collected, used, consulted or otherwise processed when you use this website. This Privacy Policy applies to your personal data processing on this website, and not to data processing that may occur on other services or web sites regardless whether they are provided by the owner of this website of someone else. The owner of this website ('we', 'us', 'our') is:
Better Collective A/S,
Tolbodgade 12,
1253 Copenhagen K (Hovedstaden)
Denmark (DK)
CVR. 27652913
This Privacy Policy is effective from 25th May 2018. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time-to-time.
Essential modifications are those that might affect your rights, obligations and state regarding protection and processing of your personal data. The essential modifications might be necessary if we, for instance, launch new services, deploy new technologies and process your data for new purposes. Therefore, if we make essential modifications to the Privacy Policy, we will send you notice through our Services, or by other means, in order to give you the opportunity to review the changes before they become effective.
In addition, from time to time we make minor modifications of the Privacy Policy. Minor modifications do not impact your rights, obligations and state with regard to protection of personal data. These types of modifications might include (but are not limited to) organizational and grammatical changes to this Privacy Policy to makes our policy easy to read. The fact that you continue to use our Services after we publish the updated Privacy Policy with only minor modifications means that the processing of your personal data is subject to the updated Privacy Policy with only minor modifications.
Data Controller and Data Subjects
By using this website you may disclose various pieces of information, including those that would be considered personal data. When your personal data is processed then you are considered a data subject and you are entitled to exercise your rights guaranteed by EU Data Protection Law and explained in this Privacy Policy. Taking into account that we determine the purposes and means of processing personal data on this website, we are legally considered as data controller over your personal data. Being data controller provides us the opportunity to process your personal data, but also obliges us to protect them in the way regulated by EU Data Protection Law, particularly by the General Data Protection Regulation ('GDPR'), and this Privacy Policy. By using this website you may disclose various pieces of information, including those that would be considered personal data. When your personal data is processed then you are considered a data subject and you are entitled to exercise your rights guaranteed by EU Data Protection Law and explained in this Privacy Policy. Taking into account that we determine the purposes and means of processing personal data on this website, we are legally considered as data controller over your personal data. Being data controller provides us the opportunity to process your personal data, but also obliges us to protect them in the way regulated by EU Data Protection Law, particularly by the General Data Protection Regulation ('GDPR'), and this Privacy Policy.
Data we process
We are processing (or might process) various categories of your data. By use of information that web browsers, mobile devices, and servers typically make available we might process your electronic identification data such as IP address, the browser type, unique device identifiers, language preference, referring site, the date and time of access, operating system, and mobile network information.
You may also provide to us information such as email address when you respond to surveys, communicate with our support team or subscribe for newsletter. Also, we may process your interactions on our website such as pages you visit.
We might process information about your interactions with other websites such as whether you visited and/or registered on websites of our partners. We may also process information related to gambling activities that you took on pages controlled by online gambling service providers that we cooperate with. This type information we process only on aggregated level. In other words, this type of your information is grouped with the same type of data generated by other users. Thus, we cannot find out details exactly about your activities on other websites managed by our partners, but we can find out general statistics about the activities of our users.
Why we process your data and how
Information about your email address and name we have to process in order to communicate with you.
When we process your IP address we may determine the approximate location of your device. We collect and use this information to, for example, calculate how many people visit our website from certain geographic regions. Processing other electronic identification data as well as location data might be necessary to present the relevant content to you (e.g. for instance to provide appropriate content for your language of choice and gambling-related content that is legal in your country).
Data generated when you visit our website is processed to improve your experience about our website, to further develop content on the website, to secure and maintain regular functioning of the website, and prevent any problems that may occur. Processing data that disclose your interactions with the website helps us to improve the website and make it easier to use - for example by adding new features that we think our users will enjoy and/or better understand user retention and attrition on the website. Also, we use this type of data to measure, gauge, and improve the effectiveness of our advertising that you may find on the page.
We may process your data about visits and activities taken on pages of our partners. This type of data serves to obtain report how many visitors from our pages visited or took gambling activities on websites of our partners that provide online gambling services. This information is important for us to generate our revenues.
Our use of cookies
Any browser visiting our Website will receive cookies from us. We use cookies because we wish to provide the best possible on-site experience to everyone who visits our website.
By the use of cookies we process standard internet log information and details of Website visitors behavior patterns. The use of cookies enable us to improve site navigation, analyze on-site behavior of everyone who visits the website, promote our products and provide content from third parties. To find out more about our use of cookies, read our Cookie Policy.
How we protect your data
We do not collect personal data in excessive manner. We only process data that we really need. We are tending to keep your data up to date and to store them securely. We do not process your data for period longer than it is necessary for the purposes for which data is processed.
We use technical and organizational measures in accordance with good industry practice to safeguard your information. Thus, we take appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure protection of your personal data against accidental or unlawful loss, alteration, steal, unauthorized disclosure or access, unauthorized use and against all other unlawful forms of processing.
We apply different levels of access control to your data. Restriction of access control is based on business needs and security requirements. We ensure you that only appropriately authorized persons have access to your data, whose knowledge and skills about data is necessary to fulfill their obligations arising out of or in connection with the performance of their job.
Legal ground for processing your data
We have a legitimate interest in using your information - for example, to provide and update our website, to improve our website so that we can offer you an even better user experience, to safeguard the website, to communicate with you, to measure, gauge, and improve the effectiveness of available advertising, and better understand user retention and attrition, to monitor and prevent any problems with our Services, and to personalize your experience.
Also, some of your data might be necessary to process in order to comply with mandatory legal obligations.
Who else may access your data
We may share your data with third parties. The third parties are categorized as follows:
Members of the Better Collective Group which includes Better Collective A/S and its subsidiaries (the BC Group) - More about members of the BC Group is available here. Please be aware that we determine the purpose and means of the processing of your data as well as deciding which of your data is going to be processed by other members of the BC Group.
Entities who help us to regularly provide, and further develop our services (e.g. analytics, maintenance, marketing, development). They are allowed to process your information as reasonably necessary in order to perform delegated tasks. Please be aware that only we determine the purpose and means of the processing of your data as well as we decide which of your data is going to be processed to perform delegated tasks.
With public authorities and law enforcement agencies where it is necessary to do so and where we are legally required or permitted to do so.
Transfer of your data to third countries
We may transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area in order to provide our services on regularly base and/or to further develop our services. We take all measures in relation to the recipients of your personal data, to ensure an adequate level of protection and appropriate safeguards as defined by the applicable data protection law and particularly GDPR are implemented.
Your personal data might be transferred to the recipient based in country the European Commission considers to have an adequate level of data protection. You may find out more about countries with adequate level of protection here.
If your data is transferred to a recipient based in US, then we aim to transfer your data in the way laid down by Privacy Shield mechanism. More about Privacy Shield mechanism is available here.
We will conclude Data Protection Agreements as necessary with recipients of your data that will include Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission and that would oblige the data recipient to provide an adequate level of protection and implement appropriate safeguards as defined by the applicable data protection law, and particularly GDPR, with regard to processing your personal data.
Your rights
Taking into account that we are a company based in the European Union, processing of your data fall under the scope of the GDPR. GDPR gives you rights with respect to your personal data, subject to any exemptions provided by the law, including the rights to:
Request access to your personal data;
Request correction or deletion of your personal data;
Object to our use and processing of your personal data;
Request that we limit our use and processing of your personal data; and
Request portability of your personal data.
If you have any questions or doubt how to access, correct, or delete your personal data, please do not hesitate to contact us via dataprotection@bettercollective.com . If you feel that your personal data rights have been breached, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority. The relevant data protection authority in EU Member States might be determined either by your place of habitual residence, or the place where the alleged infringement emerged.
As we are established in Denmark you may choose to contact Danish Data Protection Agency - Address: Datatilsynet, Borgergade 28, 5, DK-1300 Copenhagen K;
Info:    Best Online Bookmakers   Betting Previews   Betting Articles    Bookmaker Reviews    Betting Bonus
Betting Previews
Wycombe vs Tranmere Prediction & Betting Tips, 20th November 2019
Newport vs Grimsby Prediction & Betting Tips, 20th November 2019
Belgium vs Cyprus Prediction & Betting Tips, 19th November 2019
Germany vs Northern Ireland Prediction & Betting Tips, 19th November 2019
Scotland vs Kazakhstan Prediction & Betting Tips, 19th November 2019
Football-Bookmakers.com is an online betting site providing free information on
bookmakers, football betting news, betting events, tips & match previews and articles on betting.
